Hello everyone.  Let's see
what stocks Sindhi
has announced today, March 25th.
As usual, the disclaimer is that our channel is
purely informational and does not contain any
recommendations.  This is all
information, if you say it in Tamil,
it's information for today.  So, as usual, the disclaimer
is over. We are providing information only, no
recommendation, please consult
your 5. Let's go into the video.  The video is a
short video.  Let's see. First of all,
Indian
Renewable Energy Development Agencies
119 Gun Base 60 Paisa Dividend Tara.   It's on
TV and
it's with a certain person.  If you look at the financial institutions sector, the record state will
come on April 2, 2026.
If you look at the dividend yield of TVS Holdings Limited, it will be 6% higher than the dividend yield of 1486.
I think the record came on 2 April 2026 and the sector came to the holding company.
If you look at the current price of Sana Iya Limited, they had already announced a
dividend of ₹48 per share at 3318
.  1% comes from TV.
They announced the record date for that today.  The
record date for the pharmaceuticals was April 22nd
.
AV India Limited
has made a split announcement at 1:10 for 120 consoles.  The pain in the base
will not be noticeable.  They are changing something.  A
stock split into 10 stocks.  They will
adjust the price of a share in the same way
.  The recovery for that has not
yet been released.  Coming soon.
The sector has come and plastic products.
They are saying that there is a possibility that our next meeting will consider the upcoming board meeting.
IICI Lombard General Insurance
Company 1770 Can Base.
There is a board meeting on April 15th.
Both dividend results have been announced. If you look at the
sector,
Genta Insurance gave a dividend of
₹7 in June and
₹65 in October last year.
HDP Financial Services Limited has 61 shares and a
board meeting on April 15. Both dividend results have been
announced. If you look at the
sector, NBFC has given a dividend of ₹2 last year.
Iya Asset Management Limited has 864 shares and a
board meeting on April 27.   They should
announce the results soon.
The sector has arrived and AMC is there.
If you look at last year, they gave ₹10 in dividends,
and then in November, they gave ₹9,000 in dividends
.
There is a board meeting at Endurance Technologies Limited, 2328, Concourse 14.
Both teams
announced the results.  They come to the sector and
are involved in technology.  Last year,
they gave me ₹10 as a gift.  There is a
board meeting at Maintech Iya Limited, 126 Gun Base 19
.  Both teams
announced the results.
I think the sector is software.  Last
year, they gave me ₹10 as a gift.  So, there might
be a mistake, so please check it
.
There is a board meeting at Paska Limited 30388 Gun Base 20.
They are announcing the results of both matches.  Last year, when Sigta came to Auto Components,
they gave 51 Tvandas.
There is a board meeting for Pasca Limited, Nerlan Limited, 500 Gun Base, 25 more.   They
announced the results of the TV show last
year, and this year they are already in February
.  There
are opportunities for further growth. Esab Iya
Limited current price 5275 gun price 25
above board meeting.
They announced the results.  They come from the sector and
are in other financial services.
You've already given me a ₹ T this year.  So this will
be the second Tvanda.  So let's
wait and
see what they'll give us in return.
I will see you again in the morning when I finish this morning.
Thank you and goodbye.